<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on Gautam Rao</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on Gautam Rao</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/sections/aboutme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sections/aboutme/</guid>
      <description>I am an Associate Professor at the Department of Economics at Harvard University. I graduated from UC Berkeley with a PhD in Economics in 2014.
My research tries to bring insights from psychology to bear on topics in economics, particularly topics relevant to developing countries. Recent projects include studying how improving sleep affects the economic outcomes of workers in India, how the endowment effect influences consumer demand for collateralized loans in Kenya, how research findings affect the beliefs and policy choices of mayors in Brazil, and how mixing rich and poor students in schools in India affects social preferences and behaviors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/sections/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sections/contact/</guid>
      <description>Email: grao@fas.harvard.edu
Tel: +1 (857) 998-4505
Address:
Department of Economics
Littauer Center M-30, Harvard University
Cambridge, MA 02138
U.S.A.
Teaching (Spring 2020)
Econ 2338: Behavioral Development Economics
Econ 980: Behavioral Economics of Poverty and Development (junior seminar)
Information for (potential) advisees</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/sections/from-another-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sections/from-another-life/</guid>
      <description>Interactions between Organizations and Networks in Common-Pool Resource Governance, with Arun Agrawal, Dan Brown, Rick Riolo and Derek Robinson, Environmental Science &amp;amp; Policy, Volume 25, January 2013, Pages 138–146
Preservation or degradation? Communal management and ecological change in a southeast Michigan forest, with Fred Nelson, Elisa Collins, Alain Frechette, Cynthia Koenig, Mosé Jones-Yellin, Brihannala Morgan, Gita Ramsay, and Claudia Rodriguez, Biodiversity and Conservation, October 2008, Volume 17, Issue 11, pp 2757-2772</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/sections/office-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sections/office-hours/</guid>
      <description>Office hour appointments can be booked online or by email.
Online signup (students only): https://raoofficehours.as.me/
Until further notice, all office hours will be online using Zoom, at https://harvard.zoom.us/my/raogautam Note: If the above slots don&amp;rsquo;t work for you, please email me to set up a meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/sections/personal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sections/personal/</guid>
      <description>Current reason I&amp;rsquo;m behind on everything
Fearless Sidekick - Kirby passed in Aug 2016
Website: I am grateful to Xinyue Lin for building my website. Please feel welcome to use and re-purpose the code for the website, which you can find at my GitHub repository.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
